

About Me

I am a passionate and creative web designer with a strong background in HTML5 and CSS3 and a keen eye for user experience. I aim to leverage my expertise to create visually stunning and intuitive websites that engage users and drive business success.

Professional Experience

HEMLATA

Web Developer

Genoviq web private limited march 2024

As a Web Developer

Agreem Technology, Noida june 2022 - July 2023

As a Web Designer at Agreem Technology, I had the privilege of contributing to the creation of responsive and visually appealing websites. I leveraged my expertise in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to build dynamic and engaging web experiences for our clients and their audiences.

Internship at IBM, India Sep 2021 - Feb 2022

As a Web Designer intern at IBM, I had the incredible opportunity to collaborate with a dynamic team and contribute to cutting-edge projects within one of the world's leading technology companies. During my internship, I honed my web design skills, gained valuable real-world experience, and made a meaningful impact on various digital initiatives.

Projects

- https://goldenemeraldshippingservices.com/
- https://eventvilla.in/
- https://goldenemeraldshippingservices.com/Petroleum/
- https://adarshmanassevasanstha.com/
- https://goldenemeraldshippingservices.com/Commerc ial%20Brokers/
- https://www.genoviqsocialwelfaresociety.com/
- https://goldencityrealestate.com/

CERTIFICATION

- Udemy Courses Certificates
- Data Visualization
- IBM SkillBuild Certificates & Badges

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the particulars furnished by me or in my application are true correct and complete to the of my knowledge belief.

My Contact

- heml21604@gmail.com
- **(** 8851150463
- O Delhi, INDIA
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/h emlata-hemlata-2842611a6

Technical Skill

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap 5
- Photoshop
- Php, Ajax
- MS Word
- MS Excel
- MS PowerPoint
- Power BI
- Laravel

Soft Skill

- Honest
- Communication
- Team Work
- Interpersonal Skill
- Punctual

Education Background

IGNOU July 2022 - Present MCA_NEW

NSTI (W) Vadodara Nov 2019 - April 2022
ADVANCE DIPLOMA IN "IT" NETWORKING
AND CLOUD COMPUTING (ADIT-IBM)

Delhi University
B.com

 NSTI (W) Noida 2017 - 2018 COMPUTER OPERATER PROGAMING ASSISTANT

Languages

- Hindi
- English
- Punjabi
- Gujarati

Hobbies

- Listening Music
- Reading
- Watching Movies